<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrew Kirrane&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrew Kirrane&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Virtual Assistant with NLP</title>
      <link>https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/projects/github-virtual-assistant-with-nlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/projects/github-virtual-assistant-with-nlp/</guid>
      <description>Click here to view the project in GitHub
Project Overview
 Created a tool that can read questions and reply with answers from GitHub&amp;rsquo;s FAQ section Scraped examples of questions and answers using Beautiful Soup from GitHub Engineered new variations of questions through context and keywords in both the questions and answers Utilized a three layer linear Neural Network to build a model that could answer similar questions Built a client facing flask app and integrated it with a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript  Client Preview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrewkirrane.github.io/Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Andrew Kirrane. I am currently a fourth year at the University of San Diego, majoring in computer science and minoring in mathematics. Since the summer after my freshman year I have been interested in both data analytics and data science and I have had the opportunity to hone my skills at a fintech startup. In my free time, I like to work on personal projects in fields ranging from sports analytics to NLP and I have a heavy interest in machine learning and neural networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
